会有多疼?
How much will it hurt?
只是取一小块皮肤当样品而已
It's just a tiny skin sample.
你看过我给自己取的
You saw me do it to myself.
那给疼痛打分的话 你打几分
On a scale of one to ten, where one is a pebble
一是鞋子里有个鹅卵石
in your shoe and ten is the monkey
十是被你误当成你的宠物的猴子在咬你的脸
you thought was your pet biting your face off.
二分吧
A two.
吃掉一整个薄荷糖?
Eating a whole Altoid?
Sheldon行了
Sheldon,
如果我能用我们的皮肤细胞
if I'm gonna synthesize a neural network
合成一个神经网络 我需要样本啊
from our skin cells, I need to harvest them.
我做过很多次了 但是如果你
Now, I've done this dozens of times, but if you're
实在害怕的话其实你可以不取的
too scared you don't have to.
不 这是为了科学
No, this is for science.
我可以为了科学变得很勇敢
I can be brave for science.
谢谢
Thank you.
哦 天哪 好凉!
Oh, jiminy, that's cold!
想想几周之后你会多开心
Just think how happy you'll be in a few weeks
当我把我们的皮肤细胞
when I've converted our skin cells
变成功能完整的脑细胞的时候
into functional brain cells.
好吧 在你下手之前提醒我
All right, just warn me before you do it.
好
Okay.
三...
Three...
二... 搞定了
two... and we're done.
你耍我
You tricked me.
你没喊一
You didn't say one.
其实不疼 是不是? 不...
It didn't hurt, did it? No...
但是"三 二 然后就完事了"是不完整的
but “three, two and we're done” is incomplete.
你知道这种事会让我很闹心
You know those things bother me.
就好像听到"哒-哒-哒-哒-哒-哒"
It's like hearing “da-da-da-da-da-dah”
而没听到高潮...
without yelling...
好吧 一
Okay, fine, one.
谢谢
Thank you.
然后喊"完成"我们就可以走了
Now yell “Charge” and we can get out of here.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall * * We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第十季第8集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 酥酥今年脱单了吗
校对: UU今年不准备脱单了
翻译: 熊熊 单身狗言小默 AU薇
哦 天哪 我才明白
Oh, my God, I just got it.
有趣的洋葱...
Fun onions...
趣洋葱(零食品牌)
Funyuns.
等一下
Hold on.
刚才是个晃动吗?
Is that a wobble?
是的
Yes.
显然是一个重力晃动
That's definitely a gravitational wobble.
啊 对不起 我可以过一会再来
Uh, sorry, I could come back.
哦 没事 没关系
Oh, no, it's okay.
我... 我发现了一个晃动
I... I just found a wobble.
哦 需要我拿拖把来吗?
Oh, do I need a mop?
是一个重力晃动
It's a gravitational wobble.
可能象征着一个太阳系外行星
It could be a sign of an extrasolar planet
可能存在生命也许某天会以我的名字命名
that may contain life and someday be named after me.
哦... 如果上面有生命
Oh... well, if it has life,
也许它已经有名字了 是吧?
maybe it already has a name, huh?
是的 但是那个可能很难读呀
Yeah, but it's probably difficult to pronounce.
你叫什么名字?
What is your name?
我叫Rajesh Ramayan Koothrappali
Rajesh Ramayan Koothrappali.
你觉得那个行星的名字
You think it would be
会比这个还难读?
more difficult than that?
你的观点不错
Good point.
你的名字是?
And you are?
哦 Issabella Maria Concepcion
Oh, uh, Issabella Maria Concepcion.
哦 很高兴见到你
Oh, well, nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you, too.
你知道 我必须说
You know, I have to say,
因为垃圾堆里这些糖纸
based on the candy wrappers
还有垃圾食品袋
and the bags of junk food I see
我还以为在这里工作的人
in this trash, I thought the person
只有十岁
working here was ten years old.
哦 得了吧 哪有十岁小屁孩懂得
Oh, please, show me a ten-year-old who knows
把巧克力棒粘巧克力酱吃的快感
to dip Tootsie Rolls in Nutella.
好样的 我只是要
Bueno, um, I'm just going
倒了你的废纸篓
to empty your waste paper basket
然后我就不会打扰你了
and then I'll get out of your way.
哦 我来吧
Oh, please, allow me.
这里有很多吃光的卡路里
That's a lot of empty calories.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
好的 嗯
Okay, uh, okay,
我... 我得走了
I... I... I have to go.
- 好的  - 祝你好运
- Okay.  - Good luck
宇宙探索顺利
with your, um, space exploration.
谢谢
Thank you.
祝你...
Good luck with your...
工作顺利
future endeavors.
怎么样?
Did it work?
变成脑细胞了吗?
Are they brain cells yet?
如果你等我一分钟 我就会告诉你
If you'd give me a minute, I'll tell you.
哦 让我看看
Oh, just let me look.
哦 天哪!
Oh, my goodness!
我看到了颤动的黑线
I see quivering black lines.
一定是神经元
Those must be neurons.
哦 如此厚重如此美丽
Oh, they're so thick and beautiful.
那些是你的睫毛 走开
Those are your eyelashes, move.
嗯 Sheldon...
Well, Sheldon...
我看到了星形胶质细胞
I see astrocytes.
我们的皮肤细胞
Our combined skin cells are now
已经是一个简单的神经网络了
a primitive neural network.
我这么有
I have such a profound
创造力
sense of creation.
我... 就像
I ju... it's like
我孵化了一只神奇水马骝
when I hatched Sea-Monkeys,
只不过这个来自于我的基因
except that this is from my DNA,
所以就像是...
so this is like...
我生的水马骝
Me-Monkeys.
这些细胞来自于我们两个人
These cells come from both of us.
是的 但是叫我们生的水马骝不押韵
Yeah, but Us-Monkeys doesn't pop.
哦 等等!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, wait!
我们的水马骝 就叫这个了
We-Monkeys, there you go.
嘿
Hey.
我们什么时候可以在这些细胞上进行试验?
When can we start running tests on it?
我们现在就可以开始了
No reason we can't start right now.
我们应该先给它什么刺激呢?
What stimulus should we introduce it to first?
光 声 温度...
L... Light, sound, temperature...
哦! 哦! 我们给他们图像刺激吧
Oh! Oh! Let's expose it to images
让它看你和我的照片 看看它更喜欢哪个
of me and you and see who it likes better.
Sheldon 这只是一堆神经元
Sheldon, this is a rudimentary collection of neurons.
我的意思是 这很有意义
I mean, it's remarkable,
但是它的能力很有限
but it's still limited in what it can do.
我明白
I understand.
她唱白脸 我唱红脸
She's the mean one, I'm the fun one.
啊 他们又搞错了给了我们蒸西兰花
Huh, they screwed up and gave us steamed broccoli.
哦 不是的 那个是我的
Oh, no, that's mine.
真的吗?
Really?
上次我看见你吃绿色食品
The last green thing
是一粒彩虹糖
I saw you eat was a Skittle.
嗯 我不能
Well, I can't eat
总吃的像个十岁的孩子
like a ten-year-old all the time.
你在和别人约会 是和谁?
You're dating somebody, who is it?
什么?
What?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你只有在上床有戏的时候
You only watch what you eat when you're afraid
才会在意自己吃什么
you might have to take your shirt off.
是的 她说得对
No, she's right.
据我的了解
As long as I've known you,
你一直对自己的
you've always been self-conscious
乳沟很敏感
about your cleavage.
因为你一直试图
It's because you keep trying
往里面插铅笔
to stick pencils in it.
好吧好吧 那就别告诉我们
All right, fine, don't tell us.
可是没什么好说的啊
There's nothing to tell.
好吧
All right.
那西兰花好吃吗?
How's that broccoli?
超恶心的 但是我还是必须得吃 因为我遇见心仪对象了
It's gross but I have to eat it because I met somebody.
哇塞
Bam.
谢谢
Thank you.
她叫什么名字啊?
What's her name?
她叫Issabella
Issabella.
哦 你是工作的时候遇见她的吗?
Oh, did you meet her at work?
是啊 就在望远镜室
Yes, in the telescope room.
所以她是个天文学家咯?
Oh, so she's an astronomer?
对...
Yes...
这就是她当时在望远镜室的理由
which is why she was in the telescope room.
是啊 这就都说得通了
Yes, this is all making sense.
很好
Good.
那很好啊 Raj
Well, that's great, Raj.
你们一定有很多共同点
You must have so much in common.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
所以咯 我们什么时候能见她啊?
So, when do we meet her?
不不不 这都还为时过早
No, no, this is brand-new.
我们都还没正式约过会呢
We haven't even been on a proper date yet.
- 好吧 那祝你好运啦  - 谢谢
- Okay, well, good luck with it.  - Thank you.
你为什么从来不吃西兰花啊?
How come you never eat broccoli?
我都结婚了
I'm married,
我就不需要再有吸引力了
I don't have to be attractive.
你知道吗 大多数人都没意识到
You know, most people don't realize
这个技术已经出来
this technique has actually been around
好几年了
for a few years.
说是这么说 但我还是无法相信你能把普通的皮肤细胞
Still, I can't believe you can turn ordinary skin cells
转化为功能完整的大脑细胞
into functioning brain cells.
哎呀 我可是把这家伙变成了一个功能完整的男票的人嘛
Well, I turned this one into a functioning boyfriend,
所以 我就是无极限
so sky's the limit.
快看 快看 我就在这儿啦
Look, look... here I am
就站在孵化器旁边
standing next to the incubator.
然后这里是显微镜下细胞的样子
Uh, here is a microscopic view of the cells.
快看啊 把它们放进一个迷你的闪电侠T恤里面那就变成你啦
Look at that, put them in a tiny Flash T-shirt and it's you.
是啊 这个小家伙
Oh. Yeah, this little guy
已经可以辨别
can already recognize
电子传输的图像啦
electronically transmitted images
比Amy实验室里的所有其他样本都要快20%
20% faster than any other sample in Amy's lab.
我对于表现出兴奋已经黔驴技穷了
I'm running out of ways to act excited.
好啦 说我们都说够啦 你们现在怎么样啊?
So, enough about us, how are things going with you?
很好 医生说现在宝宝的头
Great, the doctor said the baby's head
朝着下方了
is facing down now.
很好嘛 你知道啦
Good, you know,
万一找不到出口呢
in case the exit isn't clearly marked.
是啊 我必须得说 能够跟某些有着
Yeah, I have to say, it is nice to share
相同旅程的人分享经验还是挺好的
this experience with someone who's on the same journey.
虽然现在我们的娃已经是细胞中翘楚
Although right now ours is testing off the charts
而你们的还在它自己产生的垃圾当中翻滚
while yours is floating around in its own waste.
你是真的在把我的人类宝宝
Are you actually comparing my human baby
跟你碗里的大脑细胞作比较吗?
to your brain in a bowl?
我逼着你摇摇摆摆
Well, I didn't make you waddle up
爬了四层楼当然是有原因的
four flights of stairs for the heck of it.
你要知道我的宝宝有着功能健全的器官
You do realize my baby has functioning organs
而且还能辨认声音吧
and can recognize voices.
是啊 可是我们的能从背景噪音中
Yeah, but ours can recognize a specific data stream
辨认出特定的数据流啊
among background noise.
我的宝宝有发育健全的
Mine has a fully developed
免疫系统
immune system.
我们的宝宝不需要
Ours doesn't need
免疫系统 因为它活在
an immune system because it lives
最先进的德国孵化机里面
in a state-of-the-art German incubator.
Sheldon 够了
Sheldon, that's enough.
行 好吧
Oh, yeah, no, fine.
那我们就只要同意 双方的创造
Let's just agree that both creations
都以自己的方式特立独行好了
are special in their own way
不去傻傻地比较他们了
and it is foolish to try and compare them.
不过 我们可不用为了我们的宝宝
Although, we didn't need to have sex with Howard
跟Howard啪啪啪 所以还是我们赢
for ours, so we win.
这很有趣啊
This is fun.
我以前从来没清理过马桶
I have never cleaned a toilet before.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
不 我从小在满是佣人的屋子长大
No, I grew up with a house full of servants
然后现在我家有个清洁女工...
and now I have a cleaning lady...
她是个可爱的女人
who is a lovely woman
我极其尊重她
who I have great respect for.
没关系的 你可以有一个清洁女工的啦
It's okay, you're allowed to have a cleaning lady.
那太好了 因为她还帮我遛狗
Oh, good, because she also walks my dog,
帮我买吃的 还帮我剪头发
buys my groceries and cuts my hair.
我觉得那应该叫妈妈才对
I think that's called a mommy.
呃...
Uh...
好吧 原谅我...
So, forgive me...
原谅我的八卦
forgive me for being nosy,
但是你那双漂亮的橡胶手套之下
but is-is there a wedding ring
是有一个结婚戒指吗?
under those pretty rubber gloves?
不 我单身很多年了
No, not for many years.
哦 所以你现在了无牵挂吗?
Oh, so, you are unencumbered?
就只有我和我儿子
Just me and my son.
我可爱孩子了 他多大了?
I love kids, how old is he?
十九
Nineteen.
这可是个可爱的年龄啊
That's a cute age.
他们能做的可多了
They can do so many things.
他在加州大学洛杉矶分校念书
He's studying to be
准备当律师
a lawyer at UCLA.
那太棒了
That's wonderful.
律师 我姐姐就是律师
A lawyer, my sister's a lawyer.
快看 我们有共同点啦
Look at that, we have something in common.
是啊 看来是这样
Yeah, I guess we do.
说不定我们还有别的共同点呢
Maybe there are other things we have in common.
到晚餐的时候 你享受吃东西吗?
C-Come dinnertime, do you enjoy eating food?
哎呀 Rajesh啊
Ay, Rajesh,
我觉得你非常贴心 但是
I think you're very sweet, but
我做着两份工作 根本没时间约会
I work two jobs and I don't have time for dating.
是啊 肯定的 我理解
Yeah, sure. I understand.
对 我也很忙的
Yeah, I'm very busy, too.
千万别往心里去 这不是针对你个人
Oh, please don't take it personal,
我觉得你是个非常好的男人
I think you're a very nice man.
我觉得你也非常好
I think you're very nice as well.
谢谢你帮我
Thank you for helping me.
晚安 Rajesh
Good night, Rajesh.
哦 是啊 好
Oh, yes. Oh, okay.
呃...
Uh...
晚安
Good night.
我也不知道为什么
I don't know,
可能是由于小便池里洁厕块产生的烟雾吧
maybe it's the fumes from the urinal cakes,
但我觉得我们之间有感觉啊
but I feel like something is happening between us.
晚安 Rajesh
Good night, Rajesh.
好吧 我会走的
Okay. I'll leave.
但是你要知道 每当我来到这里
But just know, every time I come in here,
我就会想起你
I'll be thinking of you.
你快看看好吗?
Would you look at that?
我们给它的图片有45%的白噪音
The image we gave it was 45% white noise,
而它还是成功复制出来了
and it still managed to reconstruct it.
我从来没见过这样的结果
I've never seen results like this before.
是啊 我们得在回家路上买些磁铁
Yeah, we need to stop for magnets on the way home;
这必须得上冰箱
this is going right on the fridge.
你不高兴自己参与了这个吗?
Aren't you glad you participated in this?
我高兴啊
Oh, I am.
那你知道我们的下一步是什么了吗?
And you realize what the next step is?
建立第二个环境
Set up a second culture
然后尝试复制我们的结果
and try to replicate our results.
呃 不
Uh, no.
我们应该把那扇门锁上
We lock that door,
拉下我们的内裤然后造个宝宝
lower our underpants a little and make a baby.
造个宝宝? 你在说什么呢?
Make a baby? What are you talking about?
很明显 我们DNA的结合体特别优秀啊
Clearly the combination of our DNA is exceptional.
我们的结晶也许能
Eh... Our child could be the next step
引导人类的进步
in the evolution of mankind.
这样... 它想上哪家幼儿园就能上啦!
We... we'll be able to get into any preschool we want!
Sheldon 我没准备好要孩子
Sh-Sheldon, I'm not ready to have a baby.
你准备好了 我记录了你的生理期
Oh, yes, you are! I track your cycle.
在接下来的36个小时
For the next 36 hours you're as fertile
你的繁殖力将会和施了肥的麦田一样强
as a manure-covered wheat field.
哇 我... 我甚至都能感觉到
Wow. I... I can actually feel
卵子正吓得往回爬
the egg crawling its way back up.
这我就不懂了
I don't understand.
我以为和我一起造人你会很激动呢
I thought you'd be thrilled to procreate with me.
- 这会儿不合适  - 哦
- Not right now.  - Oh,
我知道是怎么回事了
I see what's happening here.
你在吊我胃口
You're playing hard to get.
我没在吊你胃口
I'm not playing anything.
我们今天不能要小孩
We're not making a baby today.
好吧
Very well.
嗷 宝宝真是太不小心了
Oops, how clumsy of me.
我把它捡起来吧
You know what? Let me get that.
嘿
Hey.
你要去哪?
Where are you going?
我...
I...
你看了一眼我的屁屁没?
Did you even look at my bottom?
欢迎
Welcome.
- 这是什么情况?  - 嗯
- What is this?  - Oh, well,
你说你没时间去外边吃饭 我想着
you said you didn't have time to go out for dinner, so I thought
那就在这里吃呗
we could have one right here.
- Rajesh...  - 来嘛!
- Oh, Rajesh...  - Oh, come on!
我们在望远镜室!
We're in the telescope room!
这感觉就像在星光下共进晚餐
It'll be like dining under the stars.
你...你看到这 呃 这两个零了吗?
Y...You see this, uh, double zero?
“01“表示它正在闪烁
When it says “01,” that means it's twinkling.
有时候它反应比较迟钝
Sometimes it takes a while.
Rajesh 这真是太贴心了
Rajesh, this is so sweet,
但是 我现在正在工作
but you... you know I'm working.
所以我把这里都整理干净了
That's why I already cleaned up in here
走道里的其他房间也打扫了
and all the other rooms in the hall.
那可帮我省了点时间呢
Well, I suppose that gives me a little time.
坐吧!
Oh, please sit!
我试着做了你的家乡菜
I tried to cook you a meal from your homeland.
真的吗?
Oh, really?
你做了古巴菜?
You made Cuban food?
额 这得看... 古巴有墨西哥菜吗?
That depends... do they have Mexican food in Cuba?
他说“造人“的时候
Now, when he said “make a baby”"
有没有可能指的是用乐高积木造?
is it possible he meant out of Legos?
不 他说得可明白了
No. He was explicit.
明白得诡异至极而且完全没必要嘛
Needlessly and freakishly explicit.
他想要小孩做啥子呢?
Why does he need a baby?
他本人已经头发光光 一股爽身粉味了啊
He's already hairless and smells like talcum powder.
你俩真的会生出那种
Could you two really have some sort of
智商超群的宝宝吗?
super-intelligent child?
基因是一部分
Well, there is a genetic component,
但是也不能保证
but that doesn't guarantee anything.
对的 Sheldon的爸爸
That's true. Sheldon's father
还和仙人掌打过架呢
once picked a fight with a cactus.
但是那只是他的凡人父母啊
Yeah, but that's just his Earth parents.
他的外星人父母我们可是一点都不了解呢
We don't know anything about the ones that sent him here.
可我们知道他们都聪明到可以把他送走啊
Well, we know they were smart enough to send him away.
嘿 你们讽刺的可是
Hey, you're talking about the person I love
我躲了三个小时的爱人诶
and have been avoiding for the past three hours.
嗷 天啊
Aw, man.
哦!
Ooh!
Sheldon有甜头尝了
Sheldon gonna get some.
好好享受
Well, have fun with whatever nightmare's
二号门后的噩梦吧
behind door number two.
嗨 你好啊
Well, hello.
嗨
Hello.
想来点白兰地吗?
Would you care for a brandy?
不想
I don't think so.
好主意 难喝死了
Good choice, it's disgusting.
Sheldon 别挑逗我了好不好
Sheldon, please stop trying to seduce me.
谁挑逗你了?
Who's trying to seduce you?
一天结束之后 我总是会放上一点爵士
After a long day I always turn on smooth jazz
再在大腿内侧喷点麝香
and spray deer musk on my inner thighs.
闻着一股野生动物园味儿
I thought it smelled like a petting zoo in here.
你想野一下吗?
Anything you'd like to pet?
头发不行哦 上面发胶太多了
Not my hair. There's a lot of goop in it.
我受够了
Okay, I've had enough.
Amy 回来
Amy, come back.
我不懂怎么开牡蛎啊
I don't know how to open the oysters.
你第一次来美国的时候
So, um, what surprised you the most
最让你惊讶的事是什么?
when you first came to America?
大概是有多少人在意
Well, I suppose how much people care
奥普拉的完美清单吧
about Oprah's favorite things.
我也这么觉得诶
I thought that, too.
之后我有了自己的第一台华夫饼机
But then I got my first waffle maker
就没再怀疑过她了
and never questioned her again.
嗯
You know,
我这周天挺闲的
I do have some time off this Sunday
- 如果你想...  - 嘿! 我看到你的车...
- if you'd like to...  - Hey! I saw your car...
哦 不好意思 是不是打扰到你们了?
Oh, sorry. Am I interrupting?
呃...
Uh...
没事的 呃 我该回去工作了
It's okay. Uh, I should get back to work.
嗨 Howard Wolowitz
Hi. Howard Wolowitz.
哦 Issabella Concepcion
Oh. Issabella Concepcion.
是那个天文学家对吧
Oh, yeah, the astronomer.
Raj和我们提过你呢
Raj told us about you.
免费的厕纸!
Hey! Free toilet paper!
你跟他说我是天文学家?
You told him I was an astronomer?
呃...
Uh...
我明白了
I understand.
- 我该走了  - 别...别走啊
- Time to go.  - No, p...please don't.
没事的 Rajesh 我是成年人
It's okay, Rajesh, I'm a grown woman.
没必要和
I don't have to waste my time
觉得我丢人的人浪费时间
with someone who's embarrassed by me.
这玩意我可以留着 对吧?
I can keep this, right?
喂 Issabella!
Issabella!
Issabella 等等 你听我解释
Issabella, wait, wait, let me explain.
要觉得我的工作很丢人的话
If you are embarrassed by what I do,
- 为什么又要追我呢?  - 对不起
- why did you pursue me?  - I'm sorry.
说实话 我...我本来没觉得你的工作会困扰我
Honestly, I...I didn't think your job would bother me,
但事实好像不是这样
but I guess it did.
我也因此很恨我自己
And I hate myself for that.
但是我的很多事
But there's a lot of things
也会让你觉得很丢脸的
about me that would totally embarrass you.
我不信
I doubt that.
准备好丢脸丢到家吧
Well, prepare to be mortified.
我把狗粮含着 喂给我狗狗
I let my dog eat food out of my mouth,
不是因为她喜欢而是因为我喜欢
not because she likes it but because I do.
还有 尽管蝴蝶很好看 但是我超害怕它们的
Also, I know they're pretty, but I'm scared of butterflies.
不好意思哈 只是路过
Sorry, just passing through.
这是从你车上掉出来的
I think this fell off your cart.
好嘛 你意下如何?
Come on. What do you say?
让我补偿你嘛
Let me make it up to you.
你是挺执着的
You're very persistent.
我也只会这一招
It's my one move.
好吧
Okay.
这周天晚上 你可以带我去
This Sunday night, you may take me to dinner
一家豪华餐厅吃饭
at a nice restaurant.
好啊 你想去哪?
Great. Where would you like to go?
你挑吧
Your choice.
如果你喜欢的话 可以吃巴基斯坦菜
It can be Pakistani food, if you like.
呃 可是我是印度人
Excuse me, but I'm Indian.
你现在知道被冒犯是什么滋味了吧
And now you know how it feels.
难道你一点性致都没有吗?
So, were you turned on even a little bit?
感觉就像
It was like
被鼠帮皮威·赫曼打了一样
being hit on by Rat Pack Pee-wee Herman.
不好意思 这是在说是吗?
I'm sorry, is that a yes?
不是!
No!
Amy啊
Amy,
我不想这么干的
I didn't want it to come to this.
但你真是逼得我毫无办法
But you have left me no choice
只能用最最热情
but to employ the most passionate,
撩人的舞蹈了
seductive dance known to man.
弗拉明戈
The flamenco.
天哪
For God's sake,
你简直逗死了
you're ridiculous.
你俩觉得性致勃发 对吧
You guys are aroused, right?
好险啊
That was a close one.